In The Name Of God
In memory of Yadollah Najafi
Mr Etesami! Rana! Come outside!
The building is collapsing!
What's going on? What's happened?
What's the matter?
What's happened?
Get out now, the building's collapsing!
Rana! Rana!
What's going on Emad?
Rana hurry! Come quickly!
Mr Falaad, what happened?
I don't know, just get out quickly
Rana...
Come on! Come on!
What..?
Are you coming?
Mr Emad! For the love of God, someone come and help me with this kid.
I'll come, one second
Aren't you coming? I'll come with you too
No no, you go and wait outside
Tell everyone to wait outside
Where's Hossein?
I can't bring the kids down by myself
Hossein?
Hossein
Hossein get up!
Hossein get up and come!
Come on, our house is collapsing! Get up!
Get up Hossein
Go and wait in the alley
Tell everyone to wait in the alley
Mr Falaa, get everyone down to the alley
Come on Hossein
What are they doing?!
My glasses!
I'll bring your glasses
The Salesman
Written and directed by Asghar Farhadi
Guys!
Don't bring too much bric-a-brac with you
Our house has everything
Okay
I can't find it
I don't know, keep looking
Should I take it?
Thanks
You were supposed to just bring a towel and toothbrush
Should I take it?
It has my towel and toothbrush in it
Have you locked it?
Yep
Keys, keys!
Excuse me
Guys?
Hey
Hey Kati
You're alive!
When Sia said the house had collapsed, I thought we'd have to drag you from the rubble
Oh jeez... what's going on here?
It smells of gas...
It's from last night
Let's get out of quickly here then
Hey
Why have you come up?
Cut off the electricity - this is dripping
I still can't find the card
Is it not under your paperwork?
Don't go there Kati, it's dangerous
Oh my God...
You could only hear the sobbing of Mashti Hassan's wife, sitting alone with a lantern on the stable roof
and the moans of a cow that had been left behind
Sir! Is it a true story?
True? No, but it's argued that Sa'edi's characters and relationships contain a lot of truth
Sir, how can someone turn into a cow?
Try looking in the mirror?
Good one...
Seriously though Sir, how does a person become a cow?
Slowly...
Sir, are we watching the film of this story?
Good idea. I might bring it next time and we can watch it together.
Yes?
Sir, when can we watch your play?
The performance begins next week. Once we've had a few days to settle in, I'll invite you all to come.
Thank you!
Sir, what's the name?
"Death of a Salesman", who's read it?
His enemy!
Joking aside, have any of you read it?
Sir, who's the author?
Arthur Miller
Hmm... nope.
Very good.
Excuse me guys
Yes?
Hello.
Yes.
I can't speak sorry, I'm in class. If you call back in 10 minutes, I'll be free.
Yes, a ring. Silver...
Sir, what's your role?
The Salesman
What are you selling Sir?
Potatoes!
If you come then you can find out
Sir, what model is it?
What?
200???
Sir, what model is it?
What?
200???
What do you want it for?
Aren't you a salesman Sir?
Sir, his dad is a parking officer, if you tell him then he'll scrap your fines
Do you even commit driving offenses Sir?
Sir, why do Iranians call BMWs "Bee-Em-Veh"s?
Sorry, what did you say?
Why do Iranians call BMWs "Bee-Em-Veh"s?
Hey! It's fine - we learn by asking questions!
But I have no idea
Guys...
Write a summary of this story for next time. I don't want any excuses!
Could you please try and spread out a bit less?
Excuse me driver, could I swap with the man in the front seat please?
Father...
Is anyone here?
No, I think the noise was from the room next door.
No no, there's a person in your en-suite
No way, there's nobody there!
No, it's next door - they always have noisy guests
Do I have permission to come out?
Willy, something is walking in the bathroom
Miss Francis, I think your room's been painted now and you can go back to it.
But I can't, first I need to get dressed!
You can, you can!
Biff this is Miss Francis, my next-door neighbor
I said she could use my bathroom while her room was being painted.
You can go back to your room now
But Willy, I don't have any clothes on!
Okay, please leave quickly, please go back to your room
You promised me stockings, Willy!
I don't have any stockings here!
You had two boxes of size 9 stockings for me Willy and I want them!
For God's sake, will you please get out of here?
Go on
I just hope there’s nobody in the hall. That’s all I hope.
By the way, do you play football or...
Screw you!
Siavash!
What happened mom?
I've kept quiet about it but he's getting worse every night!
Come down Sadra, let's go!
Just ignore it Sanam
He thinks he can do whatever he wants, just because I'm playing a prostitute!
How's that relevant?
Why don't you laugh at the others then?
I was laughing at your clothes, not you
Shut up!
Siavash come over here!
I was laughing at your clothes, not you
Sanam...
Siavash come over here!
Sanam don't be childish on the final night
Sanam...
Sir, I fucked up... I fucked up
Sanam don't be childish on the final night
I've been rehearsing every night in this cold weather, with this child.
We're screwed!
Why are you telling us, it was her husband's doing
Let me take the k...
Get off!
Sanam don't...
I said get off!
I was joking...
She came out of the shower with a raincoat, asking "How do I get out without clothes?"
I couldn't not laugh
Go after her or she'll get annoyed and won't come tomorrow
Don't make me go out without clothes! I'm shy!
How can I go out without clothes...
Sanam!
I swear he's crazy
Did you find a place?
60 square metres / 3rd floor / no elevator. 40,600 tomans.
Where?
Amirataval
What sort of place are you at?
Just a temporary place
If we don't find something soon, we'll have to come and live in the set
Are you free tomorrow afternoon?
How come?
I'm taking you somewhere
Come on guys - one more time from the top, without stopping
Are you tired?
Nope
Oh, you're here too!
Aww kitty! Who's this?
This place has a good vibe!
Babak
Is that the storage room?
Which one?
This one
No! It's the second bedroom
Really?
Yep!
Is it not too small?
It's a two-bedroom!
So it's good?
What do two people need all this space for anyway?
Who knows, what about if we become three people...
Rana, is he serious?
No way!
Doesn't look like it
Is this door locked?
Why not?
The previous tenant's stuff is in there; they're supposed to be collecting it
Don't worry kitty, it's me
How long's it been vacant?
Three weeks
What are they doing to this city?
I wish we could tear it all down and start again
They've already destroyed and rebuilt it and look how it's turned out...
Babak?
Yes dear
God have mercy on us
When do you think they'll clear out their stuff?
They promised they'll be here in the next day or two
There's no parking, you'll have to leave your car on the road
We don't need parking, we're selling our car to cover the first year's rent
Who mentioned money?
Nobody, but still...
Hello Mr Salili
Hello
Mr Shanazari and his wife own one of the apartments here
How's it going?
Hello, hello. How do you do Ma'am?
Babak, whereabouts is the storage?
It's here, come and see
Mr Salimi?
Yes?
The door's open, take a look
Please make sure they don't turn out to be like the last one
No no, I know these guys
You said you knew the last one too
Don't worry about it
Babak, what do they do?
They're my friends, very cultured
I hope so
It's okay for a few months
But just make sure he lets us pay him for it
It looks like we've finally caught a break
Careful, don't rush
Can I help?
No thanks, go ahead
Be careful it doesn't hit the lightbulb
Sorry sir, thanks for helping
Are the keys here?
They took the one to that room with him
Where's Ali?
Ali...
Yep?
For the love of God leave it, I'll call an electrician tomorrow
It'll only take a second
Leave it, please!
If he'd said, we wouldn't have hired movers
How would I know? He sounded so sure that I didn't think he'd bail on us
Okay, what's he saying now?
He hasn't answered since this morning
Why don't you try from a different number?
Bring your phone Nana
We really need to get into the room, we've brought a van full of our things
Yes
Okay
He's here if you'd like to speak to him
Thanks
He's said all he has to say to you
What did he say now?
He signed the contract on a new place two days ago, but the landlord pulled out at the last minute
He's looking for a place, but can't come until he finds somewhere
He said to tell you not to let anyone touch his stuff
And he doesn't want to speak to you again
What's the news?
No idea, nothing for now.
Ali
Yes?
Is the screwdriver in the car?
This is enough stuff for a dowry!
I thought it was just a few bits
Maybe we should leave it...
It's fine, I'll take responsibility for it
Rana...
mumbling
These are people's belongings
What else can we do when he keeps delaying
What if he turns up?
Well he should've kept his word then
I can't carry anything heavy!
Mr?
Come and have some food
Rana dear?
Yes dear?
The charger
Go to the door and bring over one of these boxes
Hi guys
Are these the English version Sir?
Go to the office and call the librarian, then come to class
Very good guys, learn the poem for next time
Okay
Thank you
Bye Sir
Bye
Thanks Sir
Goodbye
Mr Simini?
What's up son?
Sir, I felt really bad the other day
Which day?
The day that that woman insulted you in the Taxi
Was it an insult?
The one that said we should swap places
When you got out of the car I told them that you were my teacher
And that everyone really loves you
What was your first name again?
Amid
Amid, you can be sure that a man had done something previously to make her react the way she did
And now whoever sits next to her is untrustworthy
Don't worry about it, the first 100 years of life are tough
See you
Bye
Okay
I don't know what to do about them
Who?
This woman
I called and asked when she'll clear out her stuff. She got angry and abusive.
Over what?
"Why did you touch my personal things? I'm going to lodge a complaint"
I've been constantly running around and saving her stuff from the flooding
Her problem's something else...
Who Babak, the woman?
When's she coming to get her stuff?
She's still saying whenever she finds a place
Hey
Sadra darling, come here with me
Hurry up guys, the audience will be coming in in five minutes
Emad, they're coming here again after the performance.
They've approved 3 of the 6 revisions, if you stay around after the performance then you can speak to them.
Tonight after the performance?
Yes
If it's useful, I'll stay.
Of course! If you don't then you might not be performing tomorrow
How many did they say?
Three. Guys will you please speed up!
I'll go then
Won't you wait around?
No, you'll be stuck here until midnight
Take the car then
Where are the house keys?
In my coat pocket
Have a good performance
You too!
See if the supermarket's open on your way back - we have nothing for breakfast
Yes, I said if it's open. If it's open!
Also pick up some hand soap
No not at all, I'm shattered. I haven't even wiped off my stage makeup.
Come home soon. I love you. Bye.
Anything else?
That's all thanks
Are you paying by card?
No, cash
Hello Ma'am
Hello?
Good evening, I'm your upstairs neighbor
We've just moved in, could you open the door please?
Thank you
Rana?
Rana!
What happened to you?
Please step outside Sir
You can't be in here Sir. I'll call you when we do the CT scan.
Rana...
Look at me Rana...
You can't be in here Sir. I'll call you when we do the CT scan.
Everything's fine, I'll call you for the CT scan. Please.
Look at me Rana...
Make sure you change the locks first thing tomorrow.
Why? Did someone get into the house? I thought she'd fainted and hit her head
We don't know what happened yet
All of a sudden we heard shouting and screaming from upstairs.
Not just screaming but howling. I told my husband we should go up and check, but he said it was just a domestic argument.
Then we heard some heavy bangs and I told him "Muhammad, something bad's happened!"
Who was it?
By the time we reached the stairs, we just saw someone fleeing up the road
I don't know what happened to their foot but it had bled all the way down the stairs
If I'd caught them, they'd be dead now
Then we went upstairs and found your wife unconscious, with the bathroom was covered in blood. I dressed her and we brought her here.
Let's stop talking about it anyway and thank God that nothing worse happened
Could you do me a favour please dear and go and check if there's any news from the Emergency Room
Sorry about all of this...
Have a seat
Was anything missing from the house?
I didn't notice anything
I don't think it was a robbery - what would a thief be doing in the bathroom?
Then who was it?
He was a customer of the woman
Who? What woman?
The woman that lived there before you
She had some problems... I think he came around looking for her
Don't shut the door, Ali's coming up
Sure
Come and lie down
Take my sleeve, hold this bit
Thanks
Wait, let me take your scarf off
Should I put two pillows for you?
No
Turn the light off too so she can sleep
Don't turn it off
Can I get you anything?
No, thanks
Where are you going Emad?
Darling?
Where are you going?
I'm not going anywhere, I'll be here. Do you need anything?
Nope. Leave the door open please.
Okay, thanks
Her blood pressure's low - be careful when she's walking around
Thanks for everything
Sit down guys, I'll make breakfast
No thanks, I'm fine
Come on, you haven't eaten since last night
Should I stay back and make some soup or something?
No no
Are you sure?
You must be tired. Go and get some rest
Call if you need anything
Really, let us know
Thanks again for everything
I'm buying scrap metal... Iron doors... Aluminium doors... Fences... Metal dishes...
Scrap metal... Samovars... Anything you have, I'll buy it...
Come and stand here while I use the bathroom
What are you doing?
Leave it, I can wash that
Come and wash it then
Okay, turn off the water and come out
Come and clean it before I use it
The police might need to see it
Yes?
Of course, sorry
Who was it?
A neighbor
What did they say?
I'll be right back
Sorry
I'm really sorry you were disturbed by everything last night
Not at all, what are you saying? I think you should call the police and they'll be able to track him down through the car
Sure, I'll definitely do that. I need to find somewhere...
I'd hoped that woman had taken her trouble with her when she left
Have you ever seen this car's owner around here?
Who knows, people were constantly coming and going from that apartment
I might have to trouble you again when the police come if they have any questions about exactly what you saw
Of course, it's our duty. Would you like to take my mobile number?
Yes please
I'll get going
Thank you ma'am
They should start putting these people in the stocks again and shaming them
0-900-12
Why are you out here? Come in
I'm scared of being alone in the house
Where did you go?
I went to thank the neighbors for last night
What did they say?
Nothing
They asked how you were
You didn't tell Kati what happened?
No
Okay, I'm going to the police station
We have to lodge a complaint before they'll start looking for him
How will they find him?
He left his van behind
His mobile too, but it's disconnected
Who was it Emad?
The neighbors are saying that the woman that lived here before was dodgy
This scumbag must have been one of her customers
Do you remember what he looked like?
No
Didn't you get a look at him?
Come inside, you'll catch a cold
Pass it here
Who helped me out of the bathroom?
One of the neighbors
Which?
I don't know, don't worry about it
Eat some breakfast. Have something and then sleep
I can't. As soon as I close my eyes that scene replays in my mind
How did he get in?
I opened the door thinking it was you
I came out of the bathroom, buzzed him up and then went back in
I was shampooing my hair when I realised someone had come in
He put his hand in my hair from behind and I thought it was you
But then I saw his hand and after that it's blank
Rana...
Darling, have some breakfast
Rana my darling
Sweetie
What's happening with tonight's performance
I called and told them to cancel it
No, call and say I'm coming
How when you're in this condition?
It's harder to stay at home
Put this on and we'll go to the police station. We might get held up there for a while anyway
No, leave it. Let's not go to the station.
We can't just do nothing!
I don't want to have to go there and tell a bunch of officers what happened
Did something happen that you can't tell them?
No
Then you don't have to say anything. I'll explain what happened.
I can't, it'll be too much
No, this isn't foolish talk
When I'm walking in the street I see these things clearly. They pass by indifferently, but it's as though they're mocking me with their gazes.
Why? Why would they laugh at you? Don't say these things about yourself Willy
Sometimes they pass me by as if I don't exist
As though nobody sees me. Nobody notices me
Linda?
How long are you going to spend repairing those socks?
You know doing it will make me angry. At least don't do it while I'm at home and talking to you. Okay?
Okay we'll talk about something else, for example my income.
My never-changing income. God, this is really ridiculous
Whispers a prompt
Willy. Darling. You're the most handsome man in the world to me.
You always say this to me Linda, but it doesn't help me at all.
I'll never be able to make you happy and do you know why?
Because I'm just a salesman. I'm nothing! I'm nothing Linda!
But I always tried... why are you crying?
Wait, where are you going?
Linda, come back...
Sorry, I have to stop the play. I apologise to you all.
My wife, the other actor, isn't feeling well. Please give us a ten minute intermission. I'm really sorry
Can you carry on?
What do you mean Kati? Can't you see she's not well? Go and cancel it
Do you need to go and lie down?
No, let's give her some space
Sanam dear
I'm coming
Can I bring you anything?
Kati darling...
Go and cancel the show
What happened there?
The way one of the audience members was staring unsettled me
The audience have come to watch the play, of course they'll be looking at you
They were looking at me like that man did
You said that you didn't see him
I'm really unwell, I need help
Babak, come here a minute
Coming...
Is she feeling better?
What can I say...? You didn't say a word to me about who was living there before
What's happened?
You're supposed to be my friend
Seriously, what's happened? What is it to you who lived there before?
That apartment's infamous in the neighborhood
Who's said such a thing?
Let's say nobody's said anything - why isn't this woman coming to collect her things?
I just wanted to help. Have you forgotten the state you were in last week - ready to sleep on the set?
Regardless, should you have hidden that woman's profession from me?
What hiding?
Is that not true?
Then explain it to me
Should I have passed on some unfounded gossip to you?
Where's this coming from?
Babak, I'm going
I'm coming
Why don't you go and look at Rana and see what the matter is
They said she'd slipped in the bathroom
We said in front of you we might be having a kid and you didn't say a word
You were joking!
If we hadn't been, would you have told us?
Would I have said what?
Put yourself in my shoes - how many strange men have been with that woman in the bed that we sleep in each night?
Feel free not to - I haven't cashed your check yet
Whenever you find an apartment whose previous tenants you approve of, you can leave
Hello
How are you doing
Be careful not to slip on the stairs Mrs Shahnazari, they're wet
I was actually going to ask the cleaner to come early and sort these out
But I thought you'd want the report it to the police and have them see them first
It's okay, it wasn't such a big deal
You wouldn't say that if you'd been there and had seen the state of your wife on the bathroom floor
When Mr Alimoradi opened the bathroom door, he thought your wife was dead
Say hello from me
Get up, I've made some breakfast for you
I'm heading out
Wait
Wait, I'll get ready and come with you
Where to? I have class
I know, I'll wait in the car
It's not just an hour or two, you'll get tired
Then don't go today
What?
Don't go today
If I don't go today then what about tomorrow?
The day after tomorrow?
I can't stay here alone
I don't want to be here alone
What can I do? I can get you a ticket to visit your parents for a few days if you like?
Looking like this?
I've decided - we're either going to the police or we forget this entirely
Okay forget it, but let's find a new apartment
Okay, we'll start looking
But until we find somewhere, you need to try and pick yourself up
What do you mean? It's not something I can control
It's within your power to take your medicine and not stay up all night getting worked up about it, right?
Go take a shower, I'll wait here
I don't want to go in that bathroom
I'll drop you off at a friend's place. Use theirs.
Go and tell them we've come to take a shower?
What do you want me to do?
You keep changing your mind
At night you tell me not to come near you, then in the morning you tell me not to leave you
Tell me what to do and I'll do it
Just go, you're late
It'll take a couple of weeks to find a place. You're not going to wash that wound until then?
I love you
Just think, it could've been worse
What if a piece of glass had gone in your eye or your head had been hit harder?
What would I have done then?
I wish my head had been hit harder
Come on, don't say things like that
Hello Mr Etesami
Hello Sir, how are you doing?
Mr Yeganeh gave me these books for you
Be quiet. What's so funny?
Why?
He said they're not suitable for children
Quiet!
Mr Yeganeh decided these weren't suitable for children?
Go and throw them in the bin
Why bin them?
Just throw them away
Give me your phone
Did you forget yours?
Give it to me
It's my phone
Sir, wait a minute
Give it to me
Sir we don't have any footage of you
I want to see what you have
I've deleted it
Let me see it
Sir please, I've deleted it
Sir, I have private photos on there
Put your hand down
That's not fair
Mr Etesami?
Sir?
I have personal things on there. I deleted the video.
On my mother's life I deleted it
Sir, send it on Telegram so that everyone can see
Don't say anything else or I'll throw you out
Mr Etesami
Sorry Sir
Don't interfere
Mr Etesami?
I'm talking to all of you
I deleted it
Please
Tell your father to come to the school and see the kind of photos you have on here
Sir, his dad's dead
Hi, sorry about that
Hi, no problem - if it's a hassle for you to keep moving it then you can leave it in the corner
By the boiler room
When my husband gets back he'll move it to a better place
I don't want you to have to keep going up and down the stairs
I'm going out for a couple of hours - you can take my spot
Don't worry, I'll find a better place for it
As you wish
Sorry
If you give me the keys, I can do it
Thanks
My wife said you're not going to report it
No
You're doing the right thing - they won't do anything even if they catch him
And you'll have to explain over and over why you opened the door, plus trekking back and forth to the court
Endless hassle for nothing
But he'll probably be back for his car. Call me if he shows up
I'll sort out that bastard
I'll take mine out and then come and park yours
Don't worry about it, I'll do it myself
Okay, goodbye then. Thanks
Goodbye
How's it going?
Hey, you okay? Is Rana here?
No, wasn't she with you?
She's coming on her own
Any news on him?
Who?
Babak had heard some things from your neighbors
Where is he? Is he here?
Babak?
Yep, he's in the back
Hi
Why didn't you tell me yesterday?
What should I have told you?
About the man turning up the other night
How's Rana?
The neighbors told you
They're also worried...
Tell everyone nothing happened
Then why are you holding onto his van?
Why's it still in the parking lot?
Tell them we'll be gone soon - we're looking for a new place
Where will you go?
I won't let you
Can you find the previous tenant and arrange a meeting for me?
Why?
I want to speak with her
Ask her why she did this
Did what?
Sent this thug to our house
Why would she have done that?
You said yourself, she made threats about us touching her stuff
She's not that sort of person. She hasn't taken her stuff because she still hasn't found a place. She was just annoyed with me that day.
Hello
Feeling better?
Yep, I'm fine thanks
Did you tell them happened?
No
Then how do they know?
The neighbor had called Babak
I'm not sure what they said
Emad, get dressed and come out
My outfit's not here
Kati's going to take your place tonight
And you just accepted that?
What can I do? I'm not in charge
The director wanted her to replace you tonight
Are you okay? Are you up to it? Go and let him know
No, I don't want to
Have you started househunting?
No, I will do
As soon as I get time
When you get time! As though everything's fine at our current place!
You haven't done anything
What?
I want us to go to the police, but you won't come. What do you mean?
You said you'd find a substitute teacher and pick me up in an hour
I couldn't find anyone to cover my class
Auntie?
Yes Baby?
Why aren't you acting tonight?
I'm not feeling well tonight darling
Why did you come here then?
I get bored at home
What?
Oh, I get bored here
Would you like to come to our house this evening?
Do you have Spongebob?
No, but we can go to the shops on the way home
From tomorrow evening you really need to join us again
Everything's topsy turvy. Everybody's making mistakes
Why?
I don't know, everyone's upset
You're better now, you should act again tomorrow
Mum?
Darling?
I'm going to Auntie's house
No you're not baby
Let him come with me, I'm alone tonight. I'll bring him back tomorrow evening
He can't, his dad will be picking him up to go to his house tomorrow
That's okay - his Dad can pick him up from our place
Do you want to go?
Yes!
You won't be a nuisance for Auntie Rana?
He won't be
Tell Emad we're taking the car
I'll bring his things over
I need to pee
I know, go on, go inside
Whose bike is this?
That one... is a kid's
Where's the kid?
They left here
Where did they go?
Huh?
Where'd they go?
They moved to a new house. Do you not need to pee?
Oh yes!
Go on then
Not that one, over here
Okay...
It's dark!
I'm coming...
It's scary in there
Come on
No, I don't need to go now
Let me help
No, but... I... I'll do it
Are you feeling shy in front of me?
No!
Can you do it yourself?
I'm drawing his mustache
Yes?
Come up dear
Who was it?
Uncle Emad
If it's my dad, tell him Sadra's not here
Why?
Because I love my Mom
Okay
Rana?
Hey
The van isn't in the car park
I parked it outside this morning
Why outside?
I didn't fancy moving it every ten minutes
Hello!
Helloooo, how are you kid?
Where are the keys?
Where you'd left them
How are things with my favorite?
Welcome to our house, all good?
Welcome!
Leave it where it is Emad
I'll be right back
Emad... Emad...
Let's forget all that for tonight, just leave it
I've made dinner, go and wash your hands and change
Go on darling
Ready for takeoff ladies and gentleman!
Sadra?
Yes!
Emad it's ready, come before it gets cold
Coming
Let's go and wash those hands
My hands are clean!
Let's wash them again anyway
Wow wow wow, look at this!
Thanks so much
Get your hands off it!
Rana, where are you?
Sadra, come and eat!
Helllllo
Hello trouble, have you two been having fun without me?
We went shopping and then hung out
Well done!
But we didn't find Spongebob
We went shopping and then hung out
Yes, unfortunately not
Don't worry Patrick, eventually a good day will come when you and I will find someone
Look at this Spongebob!
Look at what Auntie Rana made, macaroni!
More?
No no, that's enough
Okay, just let me know
Thank you
Wow, what macaroni!
Bon appetit!
Let's eat it all
Look at what she's made
Wow, I know!
How was tonight's performance?
Very...
It wasn't great
It was terrible
You're lying
That's how it is without you
Did you find the credit card?
No
How did you go shopping?
With the money you'd left
What money?
From the drawer
Why aren't you eating? Do you not like it?
Is it not tasty?
Don't eat it
What's up?
That scumbag had left it behind the other night
Sadra?
I've got an idea
Do you like pizza?
Yep
Then let me call the pizzeria
Don't eat that, it's not good
Do you like fries?
And after that Ice Cream?
Hello? Mum? Mummy?
Hello? Uncle? Are you there?
Muffled
Aahoo darling, it's Babak
Aahoo... Aahoo...
Are you there?
Give me a call when you get home, I'll be up late
What are you doing?
Nothing
Come and sleep
You haven't slept for two nights
I can't fall asleep
Why did you open her letters?
It's their private belongings
I wanted to find out who the hell that scumbag is
Let's say you find out how it was...
He'll say it was a mistake
He came inside by mistake?
He rang the bell and I opened the door
He must've thought it was that woman since I opened the door so easily
He came here by mistake?
Any when he realized his mistake?
Why not leave?
Because he saw the bathroom light on and a woman in there
How would he know that?
From your clothes on the sofa
If I'd just used the intercom...
If I'd just asked who it was...
None of this would have happened
Do you think it's that simple?
We can just tell all the neighbors about the intercom
Why are you talking about the neighbors?
They know what was going on in this house
If they didn't know, would that be fine?
What are you on about?
The van wasn't there
What?
Sorry
Where was it?
There
Sorry
Where did you leave it?
I left it there
Where?
Over there, where the Peugeot is
He's taken it
I have to find that asshole
Donkey!
Okay, don't speed
You'll freeze
It doesn't matter
What do you mean it doesn't matter? You'll get sick
Let's go to the public baths
No, I'll be quick. Just wait here
Hasanpoor, come here a sec
Hello
What can I do for you Sir?
Hi
How's it going?
Your dad was a traffic cop, right?
He's retired now, why?
A car hit my wife and drove off
I hope nothing serious Sir!
No, thank God
It was a van, if I give you the number plate...
If it's not too much trouble, could your Dad find the driver's address?
Sure, he has contacts in the office. Give me the license plate and he can find out
But I think you should report it
It wasn't anything major, I don't want to have to involve the police here
Okay, give me the registration and I'll call my Dad
Grab me a piece of paper and pen please
Why not work for me?
Are you crazy Charley? I already have a job
Then what’re you walkin’ in here every week for?
Well, if you don’t want me to walk in here...
I’m offering you a job
I don’t want your goddam job! I have a job! Get out of my way
When the hell are you going to grow up?
Screw you Charley
You're a big ignoramus
A big ignoramus Charley, how dare you talk to me like that?
If you say that to me again I’ll rap you one!
I don't care that you have money
You pervert
Why are you being like this?
What did I do?
Why add your own dialogue?
What did I add?
If we have a problem then you can talk to me
Don't start calling me a pervert on stage
This isn't acting, it's just abuse
Now you're feeling offended?
Yes
And if you do this again, I'll respond in front of everyone
The pervert is he who can't talk without swearing
I didn't know
I'm so sorry...
Bakery
Hi
Speaking another language on phone
Hi there
Two baguettes please
Should I slice it for you?
Yes please
Is that van yours?
How come?
There's an officer ticketing it
Majid! Go and move the van before it gets a ticket
Can you bring the keys?
Here you go
Thanks
See you
Bye
Here's your change
Thanks
XXX?
Take care
You too, I'll grab a water
Hi there, excuse me but is that van yours?
Yep
I need some stuff to be picked up, could we arrange something?
No, that's the shop's van
Not right now, whenever you're done
I work somewhere else, this isn't my job
You can't even at the weekend?
No, I'm really busy
You can find vans just up the road
My things are mostly books and paintings
So they can't be carried in an open van, they need to be protected from the rain
I won't have time, I'm busy
Money isn't a problem, I can pay
I just want it to arrive safely
I'm busy, I don't have time
Help him out Majid, what about one evening?
Why don't you give me your number?
I can call at a better time
If you come yourself, that'd be great
Do it between your other jobs bro
Try not to hit the doors and walls
What are you doing here?
Come here
Be careful, take it slow
Babak, call them to come and have some tea
You didn't need to do that
It's fine, you'll get cold otherwise
Where are you taking it all?
To the garage at my mom's place
I'll decide after that
She's not coming to pick it up?
She's busy
She still hasn't found a place
Get up, Babak wants to take away the woman's things
Get up and do what?
What's going on between you two?
Nothing, he can take the stuff himself
Rana?
Hi
Majid?
This is Mr Etesami
Are you free today?
What about Friday?
Hello?
You?
Sure, come on up
Hi
Hi there, how are you?
Have I got the right place? Majid said you wanted some things picked up
Sure, come in
Why didn't he come himself?
He was busy so he sent me
After you
No, after you
He didn't mention these stairs!
My poor old heart
If I'd known you were coming I would've told him the lift was broken
I can't use lifts either. Could I have a glass of water please?
Have you hired people to help carry?
No, I thought Majid and I would be enough to carry a few boxes
He was busy today, poor guy
Your son?
No, my son-in-law
There's no difference though - he's like my son
Sorry sir, we've just moved and all the glasses are gone
No problem, I'll drink from the tap
Where are the boxes?
In that room
Let's see if we need to call extra help
Give him a call and see if he's around. I can go and fetch him
Who?
Your son-in-law
Those guys have just set off to do some wedding shopping
Is there a caretaker that could help?
No, the building's empty
The walls are collapsing so we had to vacate
It won't collapse on us?
No
Let's have a look and see if it's even worth calling helpers
Sir
Please sit down for a second. I need to speak to you
To be honest, this isn't my line of work. I'm just doing a favour for Majid
So you can pay whatever want
No no, it's...
It's not about money
Please sit down, there's an issue I need to discuss
Hopefully nothing bad...
How long have you known him?
My son-in-law?
Yes
How come?
I want to know if you know him well
He's been after my daughter for a couple of years
Have you looked into his background?
Do you know him?
If you know something then tell me
When my wife and I left here we moved to a house where...
Where the previous tenant...
Let's say she was a woman who had lots of comings and goings
One night when I came back late...
My wife was home alone...
One of these perverts, thinking that woman was still there...
Came into my house
When my wife was in the bathroom
He came into the bathroom
Who?
That immoral son-in-law of yours
How do you know it was Majid?
When my wife screamed...
...he fled, but...
He was in such a rush that he left his van
I found his van and went to the shop
When I got there I wanted to grab him by the collar
Humiliate him in front of everyone
But...
I couldn't. I didn't have the heart
Everyone in the shop uses that van
That's why I wanted to talk to him here
And see if it was him or not
Majid's not like that
If I find out he is then I won't let him marry my daughter
How's your wife now?
I don't know what to say...
I'll speak to him tonight
Call and tell him I want to speak to him
I want to find out who's responsible
They're out wedding shopping with my wife and daughter at the moment
Give him a call
Find out who had his van that night
When did it happen?
Almost 2 weeks ago
Okay, let me speak to him tonight
Oh my God...
But I want to speak with him Sir
Wait a minute, I want to speak to him
Dial his number
I don't have his number on my phone
I have it
I told him to come here so that I don't have to embarrass him in front of his colleagues
Let me first make sure it was him
I know how to get answers out of him
I'll call him and tell him to come
Should I call him?
Should I dial his number then?
Hello Majid
Hello son
Where are you?
Yes, I'm with him now
Who's with you?
Call me when you're alone, we need to talk
Call my phone
I don't know it by heart, ask her
Okay
It's nothing...
Bye
He'll call when he's alone
By the way, what do you do?
I work out of the van. At nights I sell clothes on the roadside
During the day I'm at home because of my heart
I see
How come you don't have your son-in-law's number?
I don't have most peoples' numbers
Did you just get this phone?
No
Why doesn't your son-in-law have your number?
You told him to get it from someone
I don't know! I'm so confused I don't even know who I am anymore
Wait a minute
Won't it open?
There's no rush, wait a minute
Can you take off your shoe for a second?
Why?
I want to see your foot
I'm old enough to be your father and you're telling me to take off my shoe? Open the door!
I'm not doing anything to you, stop making a fuss
Take off your shoe for a moment and then I'll open the door
Why should I take my shoe off?
Open the door!
Come with me
This way
Sit here for a second and take off your shoe
Sit down
Sit down, sit on the step
Sit down a minute
Please take off your shoes
I'm not feeling well, stop it
Let me help
No, I'll do it
That one too
And the socks
What do you want from me?
Take them off
I'll do it for you
No!
Allow me, allow me
Hi Siavash
No, I'm busy
What time is it now?
No I'll be there, don't worry
She'll make her own way there
I have some work to finish
Yeah, I'm fine
Okay, bye
On my life I didn't mean to disturb anyone
Had that woman told you to go the other night?
She'd been sending me messages for a month
"Bring your van here, I have some work"
I texted back "Aahoo darling I'm not feeling well, I can't come sorry"
She was offended. After that she ignored all my messages and calls
She was blanking me
That night I thought I'd go and make it up to her
You didn't know she'd moved?
On my children's life, no
You opened the door and went in and saw everything in there had changed
How could you not know?
I saw there were a bunch of things lying around - the child's bike I'd bought was there
I thought she was moving out
I won't let you out until you tell the truth
If I'd had any idea you'd moved in...
I would've thought there could be a man in the bathroom
Maybe you...
My wife's clothes were on the bed
I didn't see...
You saw the clothes and figured there was a woman alone in the bathroom. She let you in...
I didn't see any clothes
It wasn't even 5 minutes - I came in, saw nobody was there... Your wife had just let me in. Why did she even let me in?
She thought it was me
I'll tell you the truth
I went to the bathroom door
I called the child. As soon as I called out, the screaming started and I ran
You went into the bathroom
Not inside, no
If you didn't enter, how did you cut your foot?
I've no idea, I only noticed it was hurting when I got downstairs
So my wife's lying to me?
Your wife said I was in the bathroom?
What would you have done if she hadn't smashed the glass in fear?
You piece of shit
On my life, I'll swear on whatever you want - I ran as soon as I realised my mistake
Tell your wife to come and ask her
I'll wait here. Ask her. I'll wait here
What do you want her to say?
My wife has said her piece. Your wife should come here now
Call her and tell her to come here right now
Why?